find-dvd.co.uk 2019-06-18

# www.find-dvd.co.uk - Privacy Policy and Cookies

## 1.0 Our beliefs regarding user privacy and data protection

  * User privacy and data protection are human rights
  * We have a duty of care to everyone on whom we hold data
  * This data is a liability, it should only be collected and processed when absolutely necessary
  * We hate spam as much as you do!
  * We will never sell, rent or otherwise distribute or make public your personal information

## 2.0 Relevant legislation

Our business and this website are designed to comply with the following national and international legislation regarding data protection and user privacy:

## 3.0 Personal information that this website collects and why we collect it

This website collects and uses basic personal information for the following reasons:

### 3.1 Site visitation tracking

Like most websites, this site uses Google Analytics (GA) to track user interaction. This helps us to understand how many people are using our site, which pages are most popular and and how they use our site.

Although GA records data such as your geographical location, device, browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. GA also records your computer’s IP address which could be used to personally identify you but Google do not grant us access to this. We consider Google to be a third party data processor.

GA makes use of cookies, details of which can be found on [Google’s developer guides](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage).

Disabling cookies on your internet browser will stop GA from tracking any part of your visit to pages within this website.

If you are under 16 years of age you **MUST** obtain parental consent before registering with the Price-Watch service.

### 3.2 Contact forms and email links

Should you choose to contact us using [our email link](mailto:support@medifusion.co.uk) then none of the data you supply will be stored by this website or passed to any third party. Instead, your message will be collated into an email and sent to the appropriate recipient over the [Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP)](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Simple_Mail_Transfer_Protocol).

### 3.3 Email newsletter

If you choose to join our email newsletter, the email address that you submit to us will be stored in our database, in a secure data centre managed by [Coreix](https://www.coreix.net/about-us/) and only used for the service you have subscribed to. Your email address will not be shared with any third parties and will not be published within the content of this or any other website.

Your email address will remain within our database until you specifically request removal from the list. You can do this by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe links contained in any email newsletters that we send you or by contacting us directly at [requesting removal.](mailto:support@medifusion.co.uk?subject=Website%20newsletter%20unsubscribe)

If you are under 16 years of age you **MUST** obtain parental consent before joining our email newsletter.

## 4.0 How we store your personal information

If you sign up to the Price-Watch service on this website then some basic, personal information (i.e. name and contact email address) will be stored within this website’s database. Individual passwords are encrypted using a private key so that even if our database was to be compromised, thieves could not associate an email address with a password.

Pseudonymisation is a recent requirement of the GDPR which we are committed to implementing where possible.

## 5.0 About this website’s server

This website is hosted by [Coreix](https://www.coreix.net/about-us/) within a UK data centre located just outside London.

## 6.0 Our third party data processors

Google are our only third party data processor. They provide analytics and statistics on how our websites are used. You can their privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy/). 

## 7.0 Data Breaches

We will report any unlawful data breach of this or any of our other websites database or the database(s) of any of our third party data processors to any and all relevant persons and authorities within 72 hours of the breach if it is apparent that personal data stored in an identifiable manner has been stolen.

## 8.0 Data controller & data protection officer

The data controller of this website is: Medifusion limited, a UK Private limited Company with company number: 04660249

Whose registered office is:  

The Data Protection Officer can be contacted at [support@medifusion.co.uk](mailto:support@medifusion.co.uk?subject=FOA%20Data%20Protection%20Officer)

## 9.0 The right to be forgotten

Current GDPR regulations stipulate that users have the right to be forgotten. If you wish to exercise this right then please log into Price Watch and click the "Forget Me" checkbox or contact our data controller using the email link in section 8.0 requesting removal. We will then delete your account, remove you from any email lists and delete any record of you from our systems.

## 10.0 Changes to our privacy policy

This privacy policy may change from time to time inline with legislation or industry developments. We will not explicitly inform our clients or website users of these changes. Instead, we recommend that you check this page occasionally for any policy changes. Specific policy changes and updates are mentioned in the change log below.

For more information see our Terms and Conditions
